A Guide to the Robert Young Clay Papers, 1789-2010 (bulk 1920-2007)
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Clay Family Research Files., Extent: 97 boxes. (Box 1-97)
  - Subseries B. Locality Files., Extent: 7 boxes. (Box 15-21)
    - Goochland County - Huguenots. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Grayson County. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Halifax County. (Box 18, Folder 10-11)
    - Halifax County. (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Halifax County - Land and Personal Property Tax. (Box 18, Folder 12-13)
    - Halifax County - Marriages. (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Henrico County. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Henrico County. (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Henrico County (Map-case 56, Drawer 5)
    - Henrico County - Will Abstracts. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Henry County. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Isle of Wight County. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - James City County - Militia Fines. (Box 19, Folder 3-4)
    - Lunenburg County. (Box 19, Folder 5-9)
    - Mecklenburg County. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Montgomery County. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - New Kent County. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Norfolk County. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Northumberland County. (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Nottoway County. (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Nottoway County - Marriage Records. (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Nottoway County - Tax Records. (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Orange County. (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Patrick County. (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Petersburg. (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Pittsylvania County. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Powhatan County. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Prince Edward County. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Prince George County - Land Tax. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Princess Anne County. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Richmond City. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Richmond City - Burials. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Surry County. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Surry County (Map-case 56, Drawer 5)
    - Alabama. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Arkansas. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Georgia. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Illinois. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Kentucky. (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Kentucky - Deaths (Iris Byington). (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Kentucky - Allen County. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Kentucky - Daviess County - Marriages. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Kentucky - Floyd County - Marriages. (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Kentucky - Lawrence County - Marriages. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Missouri. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - North Carolina. (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - North Carolina - Carrabus County. (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - North Carolina - Caswell County - Marriages. (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - North Carolina - Chowan County. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - North Carolina - Duplin County. (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - North Carolina - Granville County. (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Ohio. (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - South Carolina. (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Tennessee. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Tennessee - Marriages. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Tennessee - Bedford County. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Tennessee - Carroll County. (Box 169, Folder 15)
    - Tennessee - Granville County. (Box 169, Folder 16)
    - Tennessee - Rutherford County. (Box 169, Folder 17)
    - Tennessee - Sumner County. (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Texas. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Texas - Washington County. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - West Virginia - 1880 Census. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - West Virginia - Boone County. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - West Virginia - Fayette County. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - West Virginia - Greenbrier County. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - West Virginia - Logan County. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - West Virginia - Mercer County. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - West Virginia - Raleigh County. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - West Virginia - Wayne County. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - West Virginia - Wyoming County. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Subseries C. Subject Files., Extent: 7 boxes. (Box 21-27)
    The Subject Files include a variety of materials relating to the Clay family, most concerning Robert Young Clay's immediate ancestors. There are files related to his editing and updating of the Clay entry in Adventurers of Purse and Person, as well as Bible records, genealogical charts, letters, inquiries, and notes compiled by other Clay researchers, and early Clay genealogical compilations.
    - Addresses of Clay Descendants. (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Adventurers of Purse and Person Article. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Adventurers of Purse and Person Fourth Edition. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Clay, John 6/133. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Clay, Thomas 7/134. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Clay, Charles 13/1341. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Clay, James 14/1342. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Clay, John 15/1343. (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Clay, Dorothy 16/1344. (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - Clay, Phoebe 17/1345. (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - Clay, Hannah 18/1346. (Box 21, Folder 25)
      - Clay, William 19/1351. (Box 21, Folder 26)
      - Clay, Amy 1347. (Box 21, Folder 27)
      - Clay, Henry 20/1352. (Box 21, Folder 28)
      - Clay, Charles 22/1353. (Box 21, Folder 29)
      - Clay, John 23/1354. (Box 21, Folder 30)
      - Clay, Amey 24/1356. (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Clay, Msry 25/1356. (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Clay, Thomas 27/1362. (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Clay, Charles 28/1363. (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Clay, William 29/1364. (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Clay, James 30/1365. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Averett/Farley/Pearis 13511-13516. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - DeRoy Beale Notes. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Bibles. (Box 22, Folder 9-10)
    - Biographies. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Birth Index, 1853-1896. (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - John Bennett Boddie. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Gayle Blankenship Notes. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Ruth Clay Burrell Notes. (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Clay Cemetery (Chesterfield County). (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Chart (C.C. Clay). (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Charts. (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Charts - The Colonial Clays of Virginia and Some of Their Descendants (Map-case 56, Drawer 5)
    - Cheatham. (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Church Records. (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Clay's Mill Near Long Island, VA. (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Confederate Soldiers. (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Minnie Garthright Cook Notes. (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
    - Cousins, Elizabeth Clay Clay. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Clays of Derbyshire. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Clay (Dinwiddie). (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Fred Dorman Notes. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Clay, Edward (John Hale Stutesman Notes). (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Mrs. K. Elliott Notes. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - England. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Clay Family Chart (Bandera, TX). (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Family History of the William Harrison Gunnoe and Mary Jane Clay Family, compiled by Linda C. Gunnoe, 2004. (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Clay Family Quarterly - Correspondence. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Clay Family Settlement on the Bluestone River by William Sanders. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Farley-Clay Notes; Clay, Jonathan - Sumner County, TN; Heraldry; Tuke Notes; Filmer Charts; Argall Charts; NC Maps; Young of Bristol; Gower Notes; Clay of Southwell; Scott of Brabourne; Marstone Clay Deeds; Amelia County Marriages; Campbell County Chronicles. (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - French and Indian Wars. (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Genealogy (Early Compilations). (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - General. (Box 24, Folder 2-3)
    - Virginia Gibbs Notes. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Green Clay Manuscript. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Helen Handley Notes. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Mary McCraw Harland Notes. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Hatcher-Clay Bible. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Homes. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - The Indian Case. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - The Indian Suit. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Inquiries - VA-ROOTS. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Land Office. (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Lea (Mrs. Nesbitt's Notes). (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Letters. (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Lineage Record (Burrell-Peacock-Wilcox). (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Loyalist Family. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Marriages. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Matthew Clay: Old School Republican by Lawrence W. Williamson (Master's Thesis), 1984. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Military and Public Service Claims. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - North Carolina (Arlene Sheppard). (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Obituaries from Shirley Wilcox. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Clay - Compiled by Frances Powell Otken, 1951. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Clay, Paul Carrington. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Clay, Paul Carrington - First Compilation. (Box 25, Folder 9-12)
    - Peggy Peacock Article. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Joseph Peck Genealogy. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Percival Clay Website. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Public Service Claims. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Revolutionary War and War of 1812. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Andrew Riffe Notes. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Mary Rogers Book (incomplete). (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Clay, Ruth Ballow. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Seventeenth Century Chronology. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Showaker, Clara Clay. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Signatures. (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Social Security Death Index - Clay. (Box 26, Folder 12-13)
    - Social Security Death Index - Clay (Virginia). (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Rev. Southall Notes. (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
    - Students at UVA. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Thomas Clay vs. William Glascock, 1806. (Box 169, Folder 5-6)
    - Treasurer (Ship). (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Tucker. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Unplaced-Working (Clay. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Chancery Index. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Death Index, 1912-1940's. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Vital Statistics. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Weisiger (KY). (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Subseries D. Clay Family Society Records, 2000-2004., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 27-29)
    The Clay Family Society was formed in 2001 "to encourage research and foster understanding of the genealogy and history of all branches of the Clay family." This series includes minutes and agendas, financial reports, mission statements and by-laws, membership lists and applications, correspondence, mailing lists, and material relating to Clay's design of the Society's logo. There are also files of the Society's annual "gatherings," including those held in Williamsburg, VA, Lexington, KY, and Beckley, WV.
    - Business Meetings and Financial Reports. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - By-Laws, Mission Statement, etc.. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Clay Badge. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Clay Family Gathering, 2001. (Box 27, Folder 15-17)
    - Clay Family Gathering, 2002. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Clay Family Gathering - Photographs 2002. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Clay Family Gathering, 2004. (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
    - Clay Family Gathering - Photographs, 2004. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 2000. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 2001. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 2002. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 2003. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Greathouse, Nancy - E-mail, 2002. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Membership and Mailing Lists. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Membership Applications. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Newsletter. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Tax Exemption/IRS. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Subseries E. Ballow, Escue, Kittrell, and Young Family Research Files., Extent: 17 boxes. (Box 29-45)
    The Ballow, Escue, Kittrell, and Young Family Research Files contain much of the same types of information that is found in the Alphabetical and Locality Files, but were kept separate by Clay because of the amount of material on these four families. This series includes copies of the Ballew Family Journal published by the Ballew Family Association of America.
    - Balew, Solomon. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Balew, Solomon. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Ballew - Albemarle County. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Ballew - Amelia County. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Ballew, Bennett. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Ballew, Bennett - Albemarle County, VA. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Ballew, Bennett - Chesterfield County, VA. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Ballew, Bennett - Goochland County, VA. (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Ballew, Bill - Charts. (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Ballew, Charles - Albemarle County, VA. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Ballew, Charles Jr. - Goochland County, VA. (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Ballew, David (Charles J. Ballew Correspondence). (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Ballew, David - North Carolina and Georgia. (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Ballew, Esther. (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Ballew Family Association. (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Ballew Family Journal. (Box 29, Folder 17-21)
    - The Ballew Family Book of Journals (2 vols.). (Box 30)
    - Ballew, Giles - Goochland County, VA. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Ballew, Judith Chastaine. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Ballew, Leonard. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Ballew, Leonard m. Esther Meredith. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Ballew, Leonard and Thomas - Goochland and Albemarle Counties, VA. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Ballew - Lilly Valley - Henrico County, VA. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Ballew, Susannah - Albemarle County, VA. (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Ballew, Thomas 17344. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Ballew/Kittrell - Photographs. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Ballow. (Box 30, Folder 10-12)
    - Ballow - Albemarle and Amherst Deeds. (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Ballow - Bedford County, VA. (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Ballow - Bibles. (Box 30, Folder 14a)
    - Ballow - British Records Project. (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Ballow - Botetourt County, VA. (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Ballow, Charles - Albemarle County, VA. (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Ballow, Charles - Henrico County, VA. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Ballow, Charles - Albemarle County, VA (m. Tabitha). (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Ballow Chart. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Ballow, Edward - Powhatan County, VA. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Ballow- General. (Box 31, Folder 5-8)
    - Greenbrier County. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Henrico County. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Ballow, Jesse - Cumberland County, VA. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Ballow, John - Albemarle County, VA. (Box 31, Folder 12-13)
    - Ballow, John W.. (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Ballow, Judith m. Joshua Gossell. (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Ballow-Kittrell. (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Ballow, Leonard - Albemarle County, VA. (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Ballowe, Leonard (Daughter). (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Ballow, Leonard - French and Indian War and Revolutionary War. (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Leonard Ballow/Joanna Goolsby. (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Ballow, Leonard - Greenbrier County, WV. (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Ballow, Leonard - Smith County, TN. (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Ballow, Leonard m. Sally Wingfield. (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Ballow, Leonard Jr. - Goochland County, VA. (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Ballow - Marriages, Census, Court Records, Military, etc.. (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Ballow, Meredith - Albemarle County Tithables. (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Ballow, Owen Meredith. (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Ballow - Oxfordshire. (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Ballow (Bailleul), Peter - Albemarle County, VA. (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Ballow - Smith County, TN. (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Ballow-Stewart. (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Ballow, Thomas - Albemarle County, VA. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Ballow, Thomas - Buckingham County, VA. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Ballow, Thomas - Goochland County, VA. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Ballow, William - Burke County, NC and Kentucky. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Ballow, William - Goochland County, VA. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Ballowe (Working). (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Ballowe - Albemarle County Militia. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Ballowe - Albemarle County Tax Records. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Ballowe Bible (Tennessee State Library). (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Ballowe - Buckingham County Militia. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Ballowe - Buckingham County Tax Records. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Ballowe, David N. - Buckingham County, VA. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Ballowe - Historic Buckingham File Collection. (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Ballowe Land Records. (Box 32, Folder 14-15)
    - Ballowe, Leonard - Goochland County, VA. (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Ballowe - Nelson County, VA. (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Belew - Greenbrier County. (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Belew, Joseph - Missouri. (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Hall, Mary. (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Maxwell Littleton. (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Metcalf/Ballow/Parker Genealogy. (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Metcalf/Ballow/Parker Genealogy. (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
    - Miller, Zoe. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Slagle, Vickie Ballow. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Janice Gentry Smith's Line. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Walton, Clyde. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Escue. (Box 33, Folder 7-12)
    - Escue. (Box 34, Folder 1-8)
    - Escue - Bibles and Registers. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Escue - Census. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Escue - Clippings. (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Escue - Compilations. (Box 34, Folder 12-13)
    - Escue - Correspondence and Addresses. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Escue - County Records and Military. (Box 35, Folder 2-3)
    - Escue - Origins?. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Escue - Queries. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Escue - Social Security Death Index. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Escue - Sumner County, TN. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Escue, Thomas Lloyd - Funeral Book, 1947. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Escue Volume - Documentation. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Bryant. (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Descendants of John Catherall by Fred J. Kittrell. (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Hickey, Elizabeth. (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Houston, William. (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Kittrell. (Box 35, Folder 14-21)
    - Kittrell. (Box 36, Folder 1-8)
    - Kittrell - Clippings. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Kittrell Connections - Bryant/Snipes/Scurlock/Proctor. (Box 36, Folder 10-11)
    - Kittrell - Correspondence. (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Kittrell, George W. - Maury County, TN - Mexican War Pension. (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Kittrell/Hackett/Woodard. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Kittrell/Hickey/Shivers/Paschall/Ballow. (Box 37, Folder 2-3)
    - Kitrell, John P. - Maury County, TN - Mexican War Pension. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Kittrell, Jonathan - Will. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Kittrell - North Carolina. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Kittrell, Roland. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Kittrell - Volume 1 (Generations 1-5). (Box 37, Folder 8-12)
    - Kittrell - Volume 1 (Generations 1-5). (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Kittrell - Volume 2 (Generations 6+). (Box 38, Folder 2-6)
    - The Family of Isaac Kittrell of Granville County, NC and Smith County, TN (and Index). (Box 38, Folder 7-9)
    - Kittrell - Wilson County, TN. (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Obituaries (Kittrell). (Box 38, Folder 11-12)
    - Cadet. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Cadet - French Research. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Cadet Young. (Box 39, Folder 3-5)
    - Cadet Young - North Carolina Lines. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Cadet-Young (Working). (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Escue-Young Family Bible Records. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Gill. (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Hite-McLean-Hardy-Kimbrough. (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Jones Families of Virginia. (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Descendants of John Jones and Ann Young. (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Jones, Mordecai - Greensville County, VA. (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - McGeachie, Alta Parsons. (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - McGuire-Young Charts. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Ogier. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Singleton-Young Family Bible Records. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Swaney, Sue - Young Genealogy. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Wright, Daniel. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Young. (Box 40, Folder 6-16)
    - Young - Allied Familes - English. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Young - Allied Familes - Gill. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Young - Allied Familes - Jones. (Box 41, Folder 3-5)
    - Young - Allied Familes - Mallory. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Young, Bennett. (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Young - Calendar. (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Young - Correspondence. (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Young - Correspondence (Joy S. Starr). (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Young, D.D. - Family. (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Young, D.D. - Family - Clippings. (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Young - England (Cadet). (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Young - England (Non-Cadet). (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Young - England - Huguenot Research (General). (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Young Family Bible Records. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Young Family of Bristol. (Box 42, Folder 4-5)
    - The Young Family (Contains Clay Charts Also) by Robert Young Clay. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Young, Francis - Isle of Wight County, VA. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Young, Francis - Signature. (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Young, Francis C.. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Young, Francis C. - Family. (Box 42, Folder 10-12)
    - Young, Francis Cadet. (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Young - French Research. (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Young, Henry. (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Young, Henry - Genealogy - Census Transcriptions. (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Henry Young and Family - Documentation. (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
    - Young - Huguenot Research. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Young - Huguenot Research - Virginia. (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Young - Isle of Wight County. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Young - Isle of Wight County Clerk of Court. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Young - Isle of Wight County Personal Property Tax. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Young, James. (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Young, James - Isle of Wight County, VA. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Young, James F.. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Descendants of James Robert Young and Mary Ann Elizabeth Bentley. (Box 43, Folder 11-14)
    - Young, John B.. (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Young, John B. - Isle of Wight County, VA. (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Young, Joseph - Sumner County, TN. (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Young, Judith. (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Young, Merlin. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Young, Michael (Blind). (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Young, Michael Jr.. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Young, Michael Cadet. (Box 44, Folder 4-7)
    - Young, Michael Cadet - Lunenburg County, VA. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Descendants of Michael Cadet Young. (Box 44, Folder 9-11)
    - Deccendants of Michael Cadet Young - Family Tree (Map-case 56, Drawer 5)
    - Young, Michael Cadet - Forms. (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - "The Search for Michael Cadet Young" - Huguenot Society of the Founders of Manakin in the Colony of Virginia Meeting, 21 June 1991. (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Young, Michael Cadet Jr.. (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Young - Miscellaneous. (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Young, Moses - Sumner and Lincoln Counties, TN. (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Young, Nathaniel. (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Young, Norma - Notes. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Young - Other Families. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Young, Peyton. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Young - Records Given to Family. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Young Reunion. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Young, Robert West. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Young, Samuel. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Young, Samuel - Iredell County, NC. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Young - Sumner County Suits (Working). (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Young, Susannah - Brunswick County, VA. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Young (Swaney). (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Young, Thomas. (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Young, Thomas A. - Wilson and Sumner Counties, TN. (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Young, Thomas Cadet. (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Young, Thomas Cadet - Tennessee Descendants. (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Young - Unattached Lines and Individuals. (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Young, William and Elizabeth - Smith and Franklin Counties, TN. (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Young, William W. - Pension Application. (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Young, William W. - Sumner County, TN. (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Young (Working). (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Subseries F. Allied Families (A-Z)., Extent: 23 boxes. (Box 45-67)